[{"answer": "This is PIERS MORGAN TONIGHT.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Perfect, huh?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "No, certainly not.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "And anyone see this coming?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Well, he is an actor.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "So what are we to make of all this?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, Arnold is an interesting case because he does have sort of a larger-than-life persona on the screen.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Where do you see Arnold Schwarzenegger's position here?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, there's a couple.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "What are the projects that Arnold Schwarzenegger is currently considering?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "So I think if she continues to not be publicly anti-him then I would imagine his movie career could be perfectly OK, couldn't it?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Well, I would think so.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "From everything that you're hearing tonight of this offer that's come forward from Strauss-Kahn's attorneys, does it seem to be the kind of deal you would expect to be accepted, that he will be released on bail tomorrow?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "No, he's treated equally poor that we treat everybody in our criminal justice system.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Has he been treated any differently to anybody else would be treated in his position if they weren't well known?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "It's very unfair.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "But in terms of this guy, his reputation, he has an incredibly powerful job, if you take the presumption of innocent until proven guilty, it's pretty unfair, isn't it?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "No, I would not feel confident.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Would you feel confident at this stage of defending this successfully?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Not necessarily.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Edward Black, I mean, when you hear what Alan Dershowitz said there, do you agree with him in terms of the tactics?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "You know, Eliot --", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Alan Dershowitz?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "I've been looking forward to this.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "You're confident, are you?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "You think you're going to take me down?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "And just to describe how you thought went with this British interview, you said they sent this young limey prick who pretended to be my friend.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "UGENT: Boy, did they need me there, huh?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Mrs. Nugent is here.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "My point would be -- I mean do you ever accept you might be wrong?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "My view of America right now is so beautiful I can hardly stand myself.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "What was your view of America right now?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "I don't like about America is what is being celebrated in politics, where instead of being the best that you can be, we seem to be engineering more and more safety nets, which creates, encourages and rewards an uncaring disconnect.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "What don't you like about America?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Well, safety nets.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "What do you mean safety nets?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "And I admire --", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Have you?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "That doesn't mean to say that they are any less susceptible to being corrupt when it comes to welfare than anybody else, does it?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "You know, I do regret it on one level.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Do you regret that?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "No, not a guilt thing.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Is part of that a guilt thing on your part?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Probably, yes.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Would you bring that up if I'd been clean and sober for 50 years?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "I'm 46.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "How's this, Piers, when I graduated -- how old are you?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Because I've learned that freedom is not free and I found that the reason the whole world sucks and America sucks less is because the U.S. Constitution, the Bill of Rights, outlines an experiment where freedom rules the day of individuality and that that can only be secured by crushing those enemies that would take it away.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "And that's -- can I just come about once more to the motivation for why you now do so much stuff?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Damn right I would.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "If you have the time again I suspect now the Ted Nugent you've become, you'd go to Vietnam, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "No, because --", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "So that would be in your eyes the biggest mistake of your life, do you think?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "There is no nobler sacrifice.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Is there any nobler sacrifice?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "You bet.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "You ready to roll?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "ORGAN: No, I'm amused by your reaction.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Did you enjoy that or didn't you?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Well, let me put it in official CNN Piers Morgan interview terms, shall I?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Well, don't say you guys.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Why do you guys resist that statistic?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Not true at all.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "If you had your way, there would be 10 times as many firearms, right?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "You want everyone in America to own a gun?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "-- and I hope you don't edit this out.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "What is your position?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Not even close.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "What does Nugent want?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "What I want is the Second Amendment.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "What do you want?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Because he fell through the cracks, and he didn't -- he didn't qualify to get a gun.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "How could he be allowed to get a gun?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Well, I would certainly make it a lot harder for people like him to ever get near a firearm.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "How would you fix that?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I was born in England.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Were you born in England?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Are you familiar with Ireland?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "They're terrorists.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Is Molotov cocktails and C4 explosives -- those legal in Belfast?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Well, I don't live in Belfast.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Are those -- is that -- are those items legal in Belfast?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Would you agree drugs then to be freely available?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Because drugs are 100 percent about reducing your level of responsibility, getting high, disconnecting, and I'm a cop.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "ORGAN: What's the difference in the argument?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "No, no, there should be restrictions.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "My point about the threat of your argument is you're saying -- there's a difference, isn't there, between -- you're saying guns should be made freely available, right?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Not only do I -- the FBI doesn't believe it.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "And you don't believe that?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "We'll have a break.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Now that you know that, why wouldn't you help me create more safe areas?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "From what I can read, she's the only one you have any time for in the GOP, right?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "A good man.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Mitt Romney, your thoughts?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "You know, I agree that we should be able to demand evidence and I, like he and many others, I had not seen the official document.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Did you agree with him about the birther issue?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "I have not seen -- but she's not president.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Have you seen Sarah Palin's?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "If she runs for president I would.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Why aren't you demanding to see hers?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "No, I haven't.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Have you ever asked to see the birth certificate of any other president or presidential candidate?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "I was never active enough in politics --", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Not yet.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Because the question came up whether he -- here's what I would expect, Piers, and I think -- are you an American citizen now?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "The minute she -- the minute she runs for president.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "If you're so determined to get these questions answered, when are you going to start asking where Sarah Palin's birth certificate is?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "You will?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "Hopelessly, yes.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Were you born here?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "Probably the smartest guy out there and when he speaks, he speaks for me.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Newt Gingrich?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Right now, yes.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Would you vote for him?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "A great man.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "Tim Pawlenty?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "Because it's quintessential American politics.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Why are you such a big fan of Sarah Palin?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm keen on that.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "You're quite keen on that?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "Not at all, no.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 739, "question": "Are you homophobic?", "qSentId": 738}, {"answer": "It means I'm hopelessly addicted to women -- woman.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 743, "question": "What's a heterophiliac?", "qSentId": 742}, {"answer": "UGENT: I'd say, get the gun, let's go kill a dear.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "How would you react to that?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "You wouldn't mind morally?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "And if there isn't any water, no one will drown.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 788, "question": "What is a quaint old thing where if there aren't any guns nobody gets shot?", "qSentId": 787}, {"answer": "To stop the drownings.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 807, "question": "Why would you ban water?", "qSentId": 806}, {"answer": "A fascinating encounter.", "docId": "110518pmt", "aSentId": 838, "question": "Piers Morgan, sing this with me, would you?", "qSentId": 837}]